Guide to the Chet Huntley Papers 1912-2017
Maureen and Mike Mansfield Library, The University of Montana-Missoula
- Speeches, 1964-1973; Series IV; 0.5 linear feet
  - Speech given to: Paperboard Packaging Council of America, Chicago, March 27; Communications Explosion, Chicago, March 29; and Pharmaceuticals Manufacturing Convention, Boca Raton FL, April 1 no year (Box-folder 8/20)
  - Valentine Nebraska, undated (Box-folder 8/21)
  - Convocation, March 5 no year (Box-folder 8/22)
  - Untitled speeches with multiple drafts, undated (Box-folder 8/23)
  - Hand written drafts, undated (Box-folder 8/24)
  - Speeches with no title, undated (Box-folder 8/25)
  - "Vital Speeches of the Day", July 15, 1973 (Box-folder 8/26)
- Writings, 1965-1973; Series V; 0.75 linear feet and partial oversize box
  This series ranges from manuscript materials to magazine and essay collection articles. Chet Huntley's autobiographical account of growing up in rural Montana, The Generous Years, is prominent in this series. Materials include manuscript drafts, production proofs, promotional materials, and book reviews. This series also includes a mixture of drafts and clipped selections Huntley submitted to national magazines and published essay collections. "Somehow it Works" is a bound photo essay produced by NBC News staff, using the 1964 U.S. Presidential election as a focus for reflections on the American political process.
  - The Generous Years, Original Manuscript pages 1-99, undated (Box-folder 9/1)
  - The Generous Years, Original Manuscript pages 100-158, undated (Box-folder 9/2)
  - The Generous Years, Blue lines, 1968 (Box-folder 9/3)
  - The Generous Years, Pre-Blue Line Proof, ca. 1968 (Box-folder 9/4)
  - The Generous Years, Galley Proofs, 1968 (Box-folder 9/5)
  - The Generous Years, Galley Proofs, 1968 (Box-folder 9/6)
  - The Generous Years, Galley Proofs, 1968 (Box-folder 9/7)
  - The Generous Years, Publicity, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 10/1)
  - The Generous Years, Publicity, Clippings, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 10/2)
  - Writing for a piece in Ben Gravers book, March 17, 1967 (Box-folder 10/3)
  - Christian Science Monitor, April 6, 1967 (Box-folder 10/4)
  - "The World As I See It," Paper for the National Oil Fuel Institute, April 30-May 2, 1968 (Box-folder 10/5)
  - Article on retirement for Modern Maturity, December 1970 (Box-folder 10/6)
  - Articles printed in New York Times, 1970 (Box-folder 10/7)
  - Carte Blanche (two articles), 1968 (Box-folder 10/8)
  - "The Road to Economic Authoritarianism" by Chet Huntley, undated (Box-folder 10/9)
  - "The Pace of Productivity" an editorial by Chet Huntley, undated (Box-folder 10/10)
  - Paper taken from The Generous Years, undated (Box-folder 10/11)
  - Writing on "Northwest Industrial Development", undated (Box-folder 10/12)
  - Writing for American Airlines, 1973 (Box-folder 10/13)
  - Writing for Bob Wogan, untitled, undated (Box-folder 10/14)
  - Untitled writings, undated (Box-folder 10/15)
  - The Generous Years, Artwork, undated (Box-folder 22OS/4)
  - Somehow it Works: A Candid Portrait of the 1964 Presidential Election, by Chet Huntley and David Brinkley (and NBC News staff), Doubleday and Company, 1965. (Box-folder 22OS/5)
- Subject, 1964-1973; Series VI; 0.5 linear feet and partial oversize box
  Materials in this series are articles, reports, and general documents Huntley collected as an outcome of his professional activities and as research for broadcast scripts and public addresses. The contents of this series reflect some of the most controversial aspects of Huntley's career, such as his opposition to the American Federation of Television Radio Artists (AFTRA) strike and the Federal Communications Commission's investigation into conflict of interest allegations generated by Huntley's concurrent endeavors as a reporter and an investment spokesperson.
  - American Federation of Television Radio Artists strike, documents and correspondence, 1967-1970 (Box-folder 11/1)
  - American Federation of Television Radio Artists strike, clippings, 1967 (Box-folder 11/2)
  - FCC vs. Chet, documents and correspondence, 1968-1973 (Box-folder 11/3)
  - File on Economics, 1964-1973 (Box-folder 11/4)
  - Handwritten notes on marketing, undated (Box-folder 11/5)
  - Handwritten notes on Apollo II, undated (Box-folder 11/6)
  - Research Material: American Airlines Investors Conference, 1972 (Box-folder 11/7)
  - Research Material: American Airlines, Presentation FSAB Dinner "Air Freight Services: Future Prospects", May 15, 1973 (Box-folder 11/8)
  - Research Material, general, 1968-1973 (Box-folder 11/9)
  - Research Material, general, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 11/10)
  - Research Material, clippings, 1968-1972 (Box-folder 11/11)
  - Research Material: New York Times Magazine, March 5, 1972 (Box-folder 22OS/6)
- Clippings, 1957-1974; Series VII; 1.0 linear feet and partial oversize box
  This series includes magazine articles, newspaper columns, and small publications detailing the development of his broadcast career, retirement, economic development projects, and his death. Materials in this series were collected by Chet Huntley, his wife and family, as well as by long time friends. Most of the materials in this series are undated.
  - Editorial Cartoons, undated (Box-folder 12/1)
  - Clippings: Professional I, 1957-1964 (Box-folder 12/2)
  - Clippings: Professional II, 1957-1964 (Box-folder 12/3)
  - Clippings: Professional III, 1957-1964 (Box-folder 12/4)
  - Clippings: Professional IV, 1957-1964 (Box-folder 12/5)
  - Clippings: Professional V, 1957-1964 (Box-folder 12/6)
  - Clippings: Professional VI, 1957-1964 (Box-folder 12/7)
  - Clippings: Professional VII, 1957-1964 (Box-folder 12/8)
  - Magazine Articles: Writer's Yearbook, 1966 (Box-folder 12/9)
  - Magazine Articles: Saturday Review, December 28, 1957 (Box-folder 12/10)
  - Magazine Articles: Newsweek, March 13, 1961 (Box-folder 12/11)
  - Magazine Articles: Carte Blanche, March-April 1968 (Box-folder 12/12)
  - Magazine Articles: The New Yorker, August 3, 1968 (Box-folder 12/13)
  - Magazine Articles: Pre-Vue Billings Weekly Entertainment Guide, May 31-June 6 1970 (Box-folder 12/14)
  - Magazine Articles: Newark! The Magazine for Metropolitan New Jersey, July-August 1970 (Box-folder 12/15)
  - Magazine Articles: TV Guide, June 19-25 1965, August 1-7, 1970 (Box-folder 12/16)
  - Magazine Articles: True, For Today's Man, August 1970 (Box-folder 12/17)
  - Clippings on Huntley's passing, 1974 (Box-folder 13/1)
  - Clippings on Huntley's passing, 1974 (Box-folder 13/2)
  - Obits I (newspapers), 1974 (Box-folder 13/3)
  - Obits II, 1974 (Box-folder 13/4)
  - Obits III, 1974 (Box-folder 13/5)
  - Obits IV, 1974 (Box-folder 13/6)
  - Obits V, 1974 (Box-folder 13/7)
  - Independent Tribune Presents "Chet Huntley Scrapbook", 1974 (Box-folder 22OS/7)
- Big Sky Resort, 1965-1975; Series VIII; 0.5 linear feet and partial oversize box
  This series contains materials related to Chet Huntley's involvement with the development of Big Sky Resort south of Bozeman, Montana. Materials include property description documents, a U. S. Geologic Survey topographic map, correspondence, publicity packets generated during several different stages of development, press clippings, and "master plan" packets prepared for potential investorsùsome of the latter are bound and others are in folders. Press clippings include an array of newspaper articles, letters to the editor, and magazine features including a significant amount of material regarding local reactions to the project and protests based on environmental concerns. Written materials on Big Sky consist of handwritten notes reflecting on the Huntley's desire to develop the resort. These notes appear to be a draft speech for an investors' conference. The Lone Mountain Ranch property description includes several embedded photographs. These photographs were retained within the document to preserve their original context.
  - Big Sky Montana General Plan, 1970 (Box-folder 14/1)
  - Lone Mountain Ranch property description, 1969 (Box-folder 14/2)
  - Big Sky Resort packet, Deer Lodge Condominiums, undated (Box-folder 14/3)
  - Big Sky Resort packet, general promotional materials, undated (Box-folder 14/4)
  - Big Sky Convention Facilities packet, undated (Box-folder 14/5)
  - Big Sky advertisements and brochures, 1975 (Box-folder 14/6)
  - Big Sky Clippings I, ca. 1970-1974 (Box-folder 14/7)
  - Big Sky Clippings II, ca. 1970-1974 (Box-folder 14/8)
  - Big Sky Clippings III, ca. 1970-1974 (Box-folder 14/9)
  - Big Sky articles in "The Valley Shopper" local businesses speak out, 1970-03 (Box-folder 14/10)
  - Big Sky correspondence, 1970 (Box-folder 14/11)
  - Big Sky, writings, undated (Box-folder 14/12)
  - Big Sky: Topographic map prepared by A. Lyford of the USGS, 1965 (Box-folder 23OS/1)
  - Big Sky Resort Master Plan publication; Chrysler Realty Corporation, 1970 (Box-folder 23OS/2)
- Photographs, circa 1920-1974; Series IX; 2.0 linear feet and one oversize box
  This series contains 433 photographs spanning Chet Huntley's life, with particular emphasis on his years with NBC News and the development of the Big Sky Resort. Photos 78(IX):178 - (IX):244 & 78(IX):384 - 78(IX):432 are a mixture of family photographs, candid images of Huntley during news broadcasts, and professional promotional glossies. For preservation purposes, photos 78(IX):245 - 78(IX):275 were removed from a photo album titled "Chet Huntley in Dayton February 18, 1969." A photocopy of the album cover is included with photo # 78(IX):245. Photos 78(IX):286 - 78(IX):384 and 78(IX):433 are Big Sky development images. This collection includes modern film negative for the following prints 78(IX):1, 78(IX):5, 78(IX):137, 78(IX):138, 78(IX):142, 78(IX):154, 78(IX):205, 78(IX):289, 78(IX):290, 78(IX):291, 78(IX):292, 78(IX):373, 78(IX):377.
  - Huntley childhood photo, undated; 78(IX):1 (Box-folder 15/1)
  - Huntley teenaged portrait, undated; 78(IX):2 (Box-folder 15/2)
  - "4 Huntley children Peggy, Wadine, Chet, Marian", undated; 78(IX):3 (Box-folder 15/3)
  - "Mr. and Mrs. P.A. Huntley 50th wedding anniversary", undated; 78(IX):4 (Box-folder 15/4)
  - "Chet and his 2 daughters; Sherry on left, Missy on right holding baby" (Rik Arensmeier. Also in photo are Pat and Blanche Huntley (Chet's parents), undated; 78(IX):5 (Box-folder 15/5)
  - "3 generations Chet Sherry Rik (3 weeks)", undated; 78(IX):6 (Box-folder 15/6)
  - Chet with daughters Sherry, Missy, Father P.A. Huntley, grandson (3 weeks), undated; 78(IX):7 (Box-folder 15/7)
  - Huntley family photo, undated; 78(IX):8 (Box-folder 15/8)
  - "Huntley leading man in 'granite'", undated; 78(IX):9 (Box-folder 15/9)
  - Mrs. P.. Huntley, undated; 78(IX):10 (Box-folder 15/10)
  - Chet with mother, undated; 78(IX):11 (Box-folder 15/11)
  - young child: Chet?, undated; 78(IX):12 (Box-folder 15/12)
  - Huntley with woman in uniform, undated; 78(IX):13 (Box-folder 15/13)
  - Huntley smoking pipe, undated; 78(IX):14 (Box-folder 15/14)
  - Huntley behind the mic (ABC), undated; 78(IX):15 (Box-folder 15/15)
  - Huntley leaving ABC offices, undated; 78(IX):16 (Box-folder 15/16)
  - Huntley at a KNX function, undated; 78(IX):17 (Box-folder 15/17)
  - Huntley shaking hands with two men, undated; 78(IX):18 (Box-folder 15/18)
  - "Chet Huntley KABC", undated; 78(IX):19 (Box-folder 15/19)
  - Chet Huntley at his desk, undated; 78(IX):20 (Box-folder 15/20)
  - Huntley KGO broadcast, undated; 78(IX):21 (Box-folder 15/21)
  - Huntley on telephone, undated; 78(IX):22 (Box-folder 15/22)
  - Huntley ABC broadcast, undated; 78(IX):23 (Box-folder 15/23)
  - Huntley Radio and Television News Club award, undated; 78(IX):24 (Box-folder 15/24)
  - "Huntley interviews two GI's after witnessing a nuclear blast", undated; 78(IX):25 (Box-folder 15/25)
  - Huntley with two newscasters getting into news car, undated; 78(IX):26 (Box-folder 15/26)
  - Huntley accepting an award, undated; 78(IX):27 (Box-folder 15/27)
  - ABC broadcast, undated; 78(IX):28 (Box-folder 15/28)
  - Huntley ABC broadcast, undated; 78(IX):29 (Box-folder 15/29)
  - Huntley with two gentleman, undated; 78(IX):30 (Box-folder 15/30)
  - Huntley accepting an award, undated; 78(IX):31 (Box-folder 15/31)
  - Huntley accepting Radio and Television News Club award, undated; 78(IX):32 (Box-folder 15/32)
  - "Chet Huntley" CBS portrait, undated; 78(IX):33 (Box-folder 15/33)
  - Huntley with two military men, undated; 78(IX):34 (Box-folder 15/34)
  - "Edmund Lowe, Dorothy Bundy, Chet Huntley", undated; 78(IX):35 (Box-folder 15/35)
  - Huntley with singing sailors, undated; 78(IX):36 (Box-folder 15/36)
  - Huntley early broadcast, undated; 78(IX):37 (Box-folder 15/37)
  - group shot of Huntley with friends, undated; 78(IX):38 (Box-folder 15/38)
  - portrait Chet Huntley, undated; 78(IX):39 (Box-folder 15/39)
  - reviewing scripts, undated; 78(IX):40 (Box-folder 15/40)
  - Huntley with fresh fish, undated; 78(IX):41 (Box-folder 15/41)
  - Chet in an interview, undated; 78(IX):42 (Box-folder 15/42)
  - Chet in an interview, undated; 78(IX):43 (Box-folder 15/43)
  - Huntley ABC portrait, undated; 78(IX):44 (Box-folder 15/44)
  - Huntley with two guests in a CBS broadcast, undated; 78(IX):45 (Box-folder 15/45)
  - Chet with two movie actors, undated; 78(IX):46 (Box-folder 15/46)
  - Chet in a Marine Corps crash test seat, undated; 78(IX):47 (Box-folder 15/47)
  - "Chet presented with first edition book", undated; 78(IX):48 (Box-folder 15/48)
  - Chet in CBS/KNX broadcast, undated; 78(IX):49 (Box-folder 15/49)
  - Chet witnessing aircraft recovery, undated; 78(IX):50 (Box-folder 15/50)
  - Chet in war ship, undated; 78(IX):51 (Box-folder 15/51)
  - Huntley at his desk, undated; 78(IX):52 (Box-folder 15/52)
  - Chet at his typewriter, undated; 78(IX):53 (Box-folder 15/53)
  - "Huntley May 9, 1965 Red Square Kremlin Wall", 78(IX):54 (Box-folder 15/54)
  - NBC news correspondents, undated; 78(IX):55 (Box-folder 15/55)
  - "general election coverage Bozeman Montana", 78(IX):56 (Box-folder 15/56)
  - state of Montana address, undated; 78(IX):57 (Box-folder 15/57)
  - "Chet with Ambrose Brumfield; Reedpoint, Mt", undated; 78(IX):58 (Box-folder 15/58)
  - Chet at hotel dinner party, undated; 78(IX):59 (Box-folder 15/59)
  - Chet at hotel dinner party "Burton wheeler", undated; 78(IX):60 (Box-folder 15/60)
  - "Huntley, Howard Kelsey", undated; 78(IX):61 (Box-folder 15/61)
  - "Huntley, Battin, Babcock", undated; 78(IX):62 (Box-folder 15/62)
  - with group on skis downtown, undated; 78(IX):63 (Box-folder 15/63)
  - Portrait "Chet Huntley, June 1966" (one copy signed), 78(IX):64 (Box-folder 15/64)
  - Huntley NBC broadcast, undated; 78(IX):65 (Box-folder 15/65)
  - "Chet Huntley and David Brinkley; Nixon Inauguration", undated; 78(IX):66 (Box-folder 15/66)
  - Chet Huntley and David Brinkley, undated; 78(IX):67 (Box-folder 15/67)
  - Huntley at the news desk, undated; 78(IX):68 (Box-folder 15/68)
  - at the typewriter, undated; 78(IX):69 (Box-folder 15/69)
  - Huntley reading scripts, undated; 78(IX):70 (Box-folder 15/70)
  - at his desk writing, undated; 78(IX):71 (Box-folder 15/71)
  - Huntley and Brinkley at the news desk, undated; 78(IX):72 (Box-folder 15/72)
  - at the desk typing, undated; 78(IX):73 (Box-folder 15/73)
  - Huntley, Brinkley and Friends, undated; 78(IX):74 (Box-folder 15/74)
  - Huntley at the news desk, undated; 78(IX):75 (Box-folder 15/75)
  - Huntley in a toast, undated; 78(IX):76 (Box-folder 15/76)
  - Chet Huntley, Mike Mansfield, and distinguished senators, undated; 78(IX):77 (Box-folder 15/77)
  - "Chet in Paris via satellite 2/28/69 photo taken in NY", 78(IX):78 (Box-folder 15/78)
  - "Nelson Rockefeller news briefing", undated; 78(IX):79 (Box-folder 15/79)
  - "Fly fishing, July 10, 1961", 78(IX):80 (Box-folder 15/80)
  - Fly fishing, undated; 78(IX):81 (Box-folder 15/81)
  - Chet Huntley and Richard Nixon, undated; 78(IX):82 (Box-folder 15/82)
  - portrait Chet Huntley, undated; 78(IX):83 (Box-folder 15/83)
  - Huntley at desk with pipe, undated; 78(IX):84 (Box-folder 15/84)
  - Huntley at typewriter, undated; 78(IX):85 (Box-folder 15/85)
  - "Chet Huntley in Africa", undated; 78(IX):86 (Box-folder 15/86)
  - "The Animal Kingdom-Philip Barry", undated; 78(IX):87 (Box-folder 15/87)
  - Huntley with an un-identified woman, undated; 78(IX):88 (Box-folder 15/88)
  - Huntley at his typewriter, undated; 78(IX):89 (Box-folder 15/89)
  - Huntley at his typewriter, undated; 78(IX):90 (Box-folder 15/90)
  - portrait Chet Huntley, undated; 78(IX):91 (Box-folder 15/91)
  - Huntley at his typewriter, undated; 78(IX):92 (Box-folder 15/92)
  - "Huntley-Brinkley report 5/3/65 from London", 78(IX):93 (Box-folder 15/93)
  - Huntley at his news desk, undated; 78(IX):94 (Box-folder 15/94)
  - Huntley going over broadcast script, undated; 78(IX):95 (Box-folder 15/95)
  - Huntley screenshot, undated; 78(IX):96 (Box-folder 15/96)
  - "Governor of New Mexico 1968", 78(IX):97 (Box-folder 15/97)
  - "Governor of New Mexico 1968", 78(IX):98 (Box-folder 15/98)
  - "Queen of Greece", undated; 78(IX):99 (Box-folder 15/99)
  - Huntley Brinkley election broadcast, undated; 78(IX):100 (Box-folder 15/100)
  - "Bosses unfair to Huntley-Brinkley", undated; 78(IX):101 (Box-folder 16/1)
  - Huntley, Brinkley, Nixon, undated; 78(IX):102 (Box-folder 16/2)
  - Huntley-Brinkley "election coverage November 8 1960", 78(IX):103 (Box-folder 16/3)
  - "Huntley with then Secretary of Transportation, Volpe June 3, 1969", 78(IX):104 (Box-folder 16/4)
  - Huntley reviewing script, undated; 78(IX):105 (Box-folder 16/5)
  - "Huntley-Brinkley election coverage 1964", 78(IX):106 (Box-folder 16/6)
  - Huntley in Saigon "8/25/66", 78(IX):107 (Box-folder 16/7)
  - "portrait May 1957", 78(IX):108 (Box-folder 16/8)
  - "portrait May 1957", 78(IX):109 (Box-folder 16/9)
  - "portrait July 1958", 78(IX):110 (Box-folder 16/10)
  - "in control room, December 11, 1957", 78(IX):111 (Box-folder 16/11)
  - Huntley with two un-identified women, undated; 78(IX):112 (Box-folder 16/12)
  - Huntley, Brinkley, Nixon, undated; 78(IX):113 (Box-folder 16/13)
  - Huntley, Nixon, un-identified woman, undated; 78(IX):114 (Box-folder 16/14)
  - Huntley with Walter Cronkite, undated; 78(IX):115 (Box-folder 16/15)
  - Huntley, Brinkley and un-identified man, undated; 78(IX):116 (Box-folder 16/16)
  - Huntley with Ronald Reagan, undated; 78(IX):117 (Box-folder 16/17)
  - Huntley with Ronald Reagan, undated; 78(IX):118 (Box-folder 16/18)
  - Huntley with un-identified men, undated; 78(IX):119 (Box-folder 16/19)
  - Huntley snapshot, undated; 78(IX):120 (Box-folder 16/20)
  - "Chet Huntley reporting", undated; 78(IX):121 (Box-folder 16/21)
  - "Chet Huntley NBC News", undated; 78(IX):122 (Box-folder 16/22)
  - on telephone, undated; 78(IX):123 (Box-folder 16/23)
  - news portrait, undated; 78(IX):124 (Box-folder 16/24)
  - Huntley, Brinkley and un-identified woman, undated; 78(IX):125 (Box-folder 16/25)
  - Huntley with un-identified woman, undated; 78(IX):126 (Box-folder 16/26)
  - Huntley with un-identified woman, undated; 78(IX):127 (Box-folder 16/27)
  - at a distinguished dinner, undated; 78(IX):128 (Box-folder 16/28)
  - Downtown on skis with Rich Riese (Twins baseball player), undated; 78(IX):129 (Box-folder 16/29)
  - portrait Chet Huntley, undated; 78(IX):130 (Box-folder 16/30)
  - portrait Chet Huntley, undated; 78(IX):131 (Box-folder 16/31)
  - accepting George Foster Peabody Broadcasting Award, undated; 78(IX):132 (Box-folder 16/32)
  - "memorial service Rockefeller Plaza March 26, 1974", 78(IX):133 (Box-folder 16/33)
  - "memorial service Rockefeller Plaza March 26, 1974", 78(IX):134 (Box-folder 16/34)
  - NBC Chet Huntley "The fabulous Country" portrait, undated; 78(IX):135 (Box-folder 16/35)
  - American Airlines speech, undated; 78(IX):136 (Box-folder 16/36)
  - Huntley final broadcast "Chet and Tippy at NBC desk", undated; 78(IX):137 (Box-folder 16/37)
  - Huntley KFI broadcast (early years), undated; 78(IX):138 (Box-folder 16/38)
  - Huntley-Brinkley at news desk, undated; 78(IX):139 (Box-folder 16/39)
  - Huntley-Brinkley at cow palace, undated; 78(IX):140 (Box-folder 16/40)
  - ABC "11/4/52", 78(IX):141 (Box-folder 16/41)
  - Relaxing at home, undated; 78(IX):142 (Box-folder 16/42)
  - reviewing script, undated; 78(IX):143 (Box-folder 16/43)
  - "Huntley and Joe Oexle Kremlin Tower May 9, 1965", 78(IX):144 (Box-folder 16/44)
  - "May 9, 1965 in Red Square", 78(IX):145 (Box-folder 16/45)
  - "May 9, 1965 in Red Square", 78(IX):146 (Box-folder 16/46)
  - Huntley "contemplating script" on Navy vessel, undated; 78(IX):147 (Box-folder 16/47)
  - Huntley in interview, undated; 78(IX):148 (Box-folder 16/48)
  - Huntley snapshot, undated; 78(IX):149 (Box-folder 16/49)
  - "In front of Kremlin", undated; 78(IX):150 (Box-folder 16/50)
  - "May 9, 1965 in Red Square", 78(IX):151 (Box-folder 16/51)
  - "May 9, 1965 in front of Kremlin Wall", 78(IX):152 (Box-folder 16/52)
  - "Huntley in bib overalls, 1923", 78(IX):153 (Box-folder 16/53)
  - Huntley broadcasting, undated; 78(IX):154 (Box-folder 16/54)
  - Huntley with two un-identified people, undated; 78(IX):155 (Box-folder 16/55)
  - Huntley NBC accepting award, undated; 78(IX):156 (Box-folder 16/56)
  - reviewing script, undated; 78(IX):157 (Box-folder 16/57)
  - portrait Chet Huntley, undated; 78(IX):158 (Box-folder 16/58)
  - Huntley during broadcast, undated; 78(IX):159 (Box-folder 16/59)
  - Huntley on camera from Navy Vessel, undated; 78(IX):160 (Box-folder 16/60)
  - Huntley back yard portrait, undated; 78(IX):161 (Box-folder 16/61)
  - sitting in back yard, undated; 78(IX):162 (Box-folder 16/62)
  - broadcast from back yard, undated; 78(IX):163 (Box-folder 16/63)
  - Huntley-Brinkley: Academy of Television Arts and Sciences Award, undated; 78(IX):164 (Box-folder 16/64)
  - Huntley being congratulated, undated; 78(IX):165 (Box-folder 16/65)
  - In the control room, undated; 78(IX):166 (Box-folder 16/66)
  - in thought, undated; 78(IX):167 (Box-folder 16/67)
  - Huntley-Brinkley broadcast, undated; 78(IX):168 (Box-folder 16/68)
  - reviewing script, undated; 78(IX):169 (Box-folder 16/69)
  - Huntley broadcast: screenshot, undated; 78(IX):170 (Box-folder 16/70)
  - Huntley broadcast: screenshot, undated; 78(IX):171 (Box-folder 16/71)
  - portrait "Tippy I Love You", undated; 78(IX):172 (Box-folder 16/72)
  - pencil sketch of Huntley and Brinkley, undated; 78(IX):173 (Box-folder 16/73)
  - pencil sketch of Brinkley, undated; 78(IX):174 (Box-folder 16/74)
  - pencil sketch of Brinkley, undated; 78(IX):175 (Box-folder 16/75)
  - pencil sketch of Huntley, undated; 78(IX):176 (Box-folder 16/76)
  - in thought, undated; 78(IX):177 (Box-folder 16/77)
  - pencil sketch of Huntley, undated; 78(IX):178 (Box-folder 16/78)
  - pencil sketch of Huntley and Brinkley, undated; 78(IX):179 (Box-folder 16/79)
  - pencil sketch of Huntley and Brinkley, undated; 78(IX):180 (Box-folder 16/80)
  - pencil sketch of Huntley and Brinkley, undated; 78(IX):181 (Box-folder 16/81)
  - pencil sketch of Huntley and Brinkley, undated; 78(IX):182 (Box-folder 16/82)
  - pencil sketch of Huntley and Brinkley, undated; 78(IX):183 (Box-folder 16/83)
  - Huntley in thought, undated; 78(IX):184 (Box-folder 16/84)
  - January 1967; Huntley with two un-identified elders, 78(IX):185 (Box-folder 16/85)
  - portrait Chet Huntley, undated; 78(IX):186 (Box-folder 16/86)
  - portrait Chet Huntley, undated; 78(IX):187 (Box-folder 16/87)
  - Huntley Brinkley broadcasting, undated; 78(IX):188 (Box-folder 16/88)
  - portrait Chet Huntley, undated; 78(IX):189 (Box-folder 16/89)
  - portrait Chet Huntley, undated; 78(IX):190 (Box-folder 16/90)
  - Huntley-Brinkley with two un-identified men, undated; 78(IX):191 (Box-folder 16/91)
  - "Huntley school house restored: Saco, Montana", undated; 78(IX):192 (Box-folder 16/92)